Like most of Canada, Vancouver and its area is extremely safe
カナダの他の地域と同様に、バンクーバーとその周辺は安全です
Violent crimes are rare. However, like any large urban city
凶暴な犯罪はまれですが、都市なので
petty crimes are common
軽犯罪はおこります
Areas such as downtown east side of Hasting street
ダウンタウンのヘイスティングストリートやイーストサイドなどのエリアは
are to be avoided walking late at night.
夜遅くまで歩いてはいけません
Transportation and taxis are generally very safe in Vancouver
バンクーバーの交通機関や、タクシーも安全に使用ができます
and there are many apps used for navigating the cities.
また、都市を便利に移動できるアプリも沢山あります
Students have many opportunities to familiarize themselves with Vancouver before exploring on their own
学生は、一人で移動する前に、バンクーバー周辺を
as many of our weekend activities are held in and around the city
週末のアクティビティーなどを通じて、慣れる機会があります
led by our first-aid trained staff.
アクティビティーへは、ファーストエイドを行えるスタッフが引率します
Bodwell High School is located in the city of North Vancouver
Bodwell High Schoolはノースバンクーバー市にあります
just across the water on the north side of downtown.
ダウンタウンの海を挟んで、北側に位置しています
North Vancouver is accessible from downtown by the seabus
ノースバンクーバーへは、ダウンタウンからシーバス（水上バス）や
or by crossing the Lion's Gate bridge
または、バスでライオンズゲートブリッジを通り、来ることができます
It is in a quiet neighbourhood at a roundabout corner
閑静な場所に、学校はあります
with a pedestrian trail running along a sea wall at the back of the school
学校の裏側には、海沿に遊歩道があり
Students have their own free time after classes and clubs before their study hall and on weekends
授業・クラブの後、週末にのんびりと時間を過ごす事ができます
They are free to go out and explore
自由時間には、外出もかのうです
but we ask them to swipe their key FOBs when they leave and return to the school
ただ、外出の際、戻ってきた際には、FOBをスキャンする必要があります
so staff is aware of their whereabouts.
その為、どの生徒が校舎にいるかが把握できます
For their safety outside the school, we conduct workshops
また、学校外での安全のために、ワークショップも実施しています
to ensure they are aware how to avoid danger
危険を回避する方法を、教えたり
and what to do in the case of getting lost.
迷子になった場合の対処方法などを話します
Students can call the school anytime - we are reachable 24 hours a day-
学生はいつでも（24時間）学校に電話することができます
use Google Maps, get a taxi,  or simply ask around
勿論、グーグルマップを使ったり、タクシーを使用したり、お店の人に聞くことも可能です
Canadians are generally very kind and willing to assist.
カナダ人は、とても親切ですので、困っていると助けてくれます
Students should exercise common sense when outside the school
ただ、常識的な判断が必要な場合もあります
and not hesitate to call 911 if they find themselves in a dangerous or emergency situation.
危険な状況や緊急事態に遭遇した場合は、911に電話する必要があります
Notifying friends or staff when leaving the campus is a good habit for students
また、外出する際、友人やスタッフに通知すると、安心です
At night, we require every student to follow curfew
門限後は、夜間外出禁止となります
and be back to their boarding by specific times for their safety
門限前に、安全の為、寮に戻る事が必要です
All new students are assigned a locker
学校では、ロッカーが割り当てられるので
where they can put away or lock their valuables or personal items
貴重品や身の回り品の管理は、ロッカーを使用してください
It is not safe to leave valuables out in the open or in common areas
貴重品を、屋外または共用エリアに放置する事は避けて下さい
During your child's stay here, they may get a bike, skateboard, rollerblade or other large equipment
滞在中、自転車、スケートボード、ローラーブレード、その他の機器を購入した場合、
The school has safe storage for these items
学校で、安全に保管できる場所を提供しています
We also require them to adhere to the city's by-laws
ただ、こちらの交通法に従う必要があります
such as wearing a helmet while riding their bicycles and following traffic laws.
自転車、スケートボードなどに乗る場合は、ヘルメット着用が必須です
School staff is here to assist your child in creating a safe, successful, memorable life here at Bodwell.
学校スタッフは、Bodwellで安全で、有意義な留学生活を過ごせる様、サポートをしています